ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
Now, who can answer this problem?
Anya Forger?
3/3!
Huh. That's completely wrong.
So Twilight, how is
your daughter's academic performance?
Headquarters estimates that eight Stellas
should be achieved in about four months.
Four-- That's no problem.
You've become a terrible liar.
I'm sure she'll be able to get
eight Tonitos in two months.
Never mind. By the way,
this morning, an informant
at City Hall was hit.
The enemy is tightening their grip.
Beware, Twilight.
In addition to the city,
there's no telling if there will be
surveillance within Eden Academy as well.
The counterintelligence agencies
in this country are formidable.
What do you guys want?
We're the National Security Agency.
Jim Hayward?
We're going to bring you in
on suspicion of espionage.
What?! A spy?
What are you talking about? Hey!
Stop! Let go!
Your defense will be heard
at the government building.
…and that just happened this morning!
It was so scary!
I heard that the finance department member
who was taken away was leaking
documents from the government.
What a bad person!
Good morning.
Oh, good morning!
Good morning, Camilla.
Oh by the way, Yor,
my boyfriend told me that you haven't even
told your brother about your marriage?
Oh, shoot! I forgot!
Huh? You forgot… For a year?
What shall I do?
Apparently,
he said that he'd call here later.
That's right! I haven't even given him
my new home phone number!
I was so relieved at getting married
that I forgot!
Hey, is your brother handsome?
Aw, how cute!
Yes, Yuri is very cute.
He's always right by my side saying "Sis!"
Ew, he loves his sister a bit too much…
Never mind.
How can she forget to tell him about
her marriage when he adores her so much.
Now, let's start again from the beginning.
What type of files and how many copies
were taken out of the government office?
What's the name and description of
your client and how did you contact them?
When, where and how many times
did you meet with them?
Take me home.
The National Security Agency.
The organization aims to
maintain national security,
and its main task is to hunt down
spies and monitor citizens.
Assault, wiretapping, intimidation,
and torture are routine for them,
and out of fear,
the citizens call them the Secret Police.
Hello, Lieutenant. Boss wants me
to take over the interrogation.
Okay. Then,
I'll leave the rest to you,
Second Lieutenant Briar.
Yes, sir! I'll do my best!
Yuri Briar, 20 years old.
The man was in the Secret Police.
Why did the boss let that
naive guy join the team?
I admit he's brilliant, but honestly, he's
still a kid… Wasn't he a former elite of
the Ministry of Foreign Affairs
who had a major leap in his career?
The boss said…
Huh? Well, isn't Yuri adorable?
He's like a dog.
So, that's that.
I see…
I guess our organization needs
guys like him too.
Also, when he sets his mind to something,
he does it well.
It's like he loses his perspective…
-Hello, Mr. Hayward.
-I'm not going to say a word!
My sister works
at the same City Hall as you do!
-Huh?
-Do you know her?
She's beautiful and kind.
I'm proud to call her my sister!
I'm actually going over there today
to celebrate her marriage!
I haven't seen her in a while
so I'm really excited!
So, I'd like to
wrap this up quickly and go home.
Why don't you just tell me everything?
I don't know anything!
Here are some photos
from your transaction.
This is you, right, Mr. Hayward?
Hey! Since when did you have all this
important photographic evidence?
I'm sorry. I forgot to turn them in.
It's better for you to be honest.
So I just passed on the documents
as instructed and was paid in return.
The only thing I know about him is that
he's from the West.
I don't even know his name.
Did that man
have anything particular
about his speech or body language?
Maybe he didn't seem his age?
Uh, no, not really…
I see. Then,
have you heard the name Twilight?
Huh? Who?
A spy for the West.
He seems to be a master of disguise.
He is the devil who is responsible
for throwing this country into chaos.
You could say that he is our arch nemesis.
If I can help you arrest him,
will my crimes be forgotten?!
-Do you know something?
-Wait. Let me remember… Um…
Be aware that if you lie,
you'll be charged with even more crimes.
I just wanted money to hang out with some
women! I didn't mean to cause trouble!
Don't you have a wife?
You're a man! You understand, don't you?
I was just passing along some paper.
I'm no political offender!
Give me a break! Please!
Mr. Hayward.
I actually haven't told my sister
that I work for
the National Security Agency.
I don't want her to worry
because it's a dangerous job,
and most of all
I don't want her to know
I'm doing dirty work!
Mr. Hayward.
What you have done is treason.
It may be a piece of paper to you,
but it could put many lives
in our country at risk!
Do you understand?
I'm not like you.
I actually love my family… My sister.
I'll do anything to protect this country
where my sister resides.
And I mean anything.
No matter how much you harm me,
I'll never sell out my partners!
You're so stubborn, Bondman!
If only she'd concentrate this much
on her studies.
There are two bullets left!
How many bullets does
Bondman's pistol carry?
Hm? I believe his gun can
hold up to eight bullets.
2/8!
That's right! That's correct!
The number of remaining bullets are 2/8!
How do you know that phrase…?
Is it easier for her
if she relates it to her cartoons?
We're in trouble, Loid!
Welcome home, Yor.
Number of remaining bullets are 2/8!
Apparently, Yuri, my younger brother,
is coming to our house today!
Today?!
…so that's why
he's saying
he wants to come today to celebrate.
What shall we do?
Do you think he'll find out we're lying?
Don't worry. I've prepared
a "friendly spouse set"
for such occasions.
Father and Mother are lovey-dovey.
-We're not!
Mother's brother still hasn't come?
He's your uncle.
Uncle…
It's late so you can go to bed.
Anya wants to welcome Uncle too…
It seems like he's working late…
I lost control back there
and now I'm late…
But… I finally get to see Sis!
It's been so long! Yay!
The rib that Sis once broke tingles.
My whole body is numb remembering
the love that she wrapped me in!
Anyway, I wonder why Sis didn't tell me
about her marriage for an entire year…
Maybe he's a nefarious person
whom she can't introduce me to?
I'll eliminate all threats
from this country where Sis resides.
That goes for her partner as well.
Loid Forger. If he's a son of a gun
threatening my sister,
I'll have him thrown in jail immediately!
No, relax. She can't find out about
the other side of me.
In order to protect
our happiness and my job,
I must keep this side of myself hidden!
Yuri Briar.
The only relative of the Forger family.
The closer you are, the more likely
you are to be exposed. We must be careful.
I can't afford to lose this family
that I've built up so well.
We all have a side of ourselves
that we don't show anyone.
Whether it's towards our friends, lovers,
or even family,
we hide our true feelings and true nature
with fake smiles and deception.
And that's how the world is maintaining
its temporary peace.
Foreign Minister Windsor held a meeting
with Westalis Foreign Minister Blanz
on June 6th to normalize
diplomatic relations…
-I'll see…
-I'll determine…
-If this man is detrimental or not.
-If he's fit to be my sister's husband.
No, there's no way he's fit for that.
I'll take your coat and bags.
Oh, it's fine. Thank you.
I can quickly prepare something to eat
so the two of you can go ahead and relax.
Please don't worry about me.
Why would I eat something you cooked?
Yuri, you're scowling.
You must be nervous.
No I'm not!
Oh, no. My hostility was on my face.
-Please, relax.
-I'm still highly strung.
It was that interrogation.
-I have to act like a nice wife!
-I have to act like a public servant!
There's no way I can tell him that
I only got married
so I could continue my job as an assassin!
Thank you for the flowers, Yuri.
But Sis, I haven't acknowledged
your marriage yet.
Why didn't you say anything
for an entire year?
I can't understand it
unless you give me an explanation!
It's a legitimate response. Now…
Regarding your brother,
why don't you just tell him everything?
I'm sure that your brother would
understand that the issue of
a single woman being viewed
with suspicion by the public
is a serious one in this day and age.
No!
My brother can be a bit sensitive…
He'll be distraught if he finds out
that I married someone that
I don't even love…
That might end up causing you some trouble
and I also don't want my brother to worry.
Don't worry!
I have a great excuse for all of this!
I know Yuri the best,
so please leave it to me!
I'm counting on you, Yor.
So why was it, Sis?
Why didn't you tell me?
It was because…
I forgot to!
Huh? Yeah. Um…
Then how about when
we spoke on the phone last time?
Why didn't you tell me
you had a husband then?
That was because…
I forgot that I forgot to tell you
about my marriage.
If you say so, Sis! I understand.
-I'm sorry!
-He's convinced by that?!
The man had no sense of logic
towards his sister.
Oh, you're so goofy, Sis!
This is normal in the Briar household?!
Thank you for waiting.
Ugh. Don't intrude on
my fun time with Sis!
No…
If I continue to be rude to him,
Sis might not like me anymore…
I have to pretend…
Isn't Loid's cooking delicious?
Don't think I'll acknowledge you
with just your cooking, you outcast!
That's right, I brought some wine!
Here you are.
How kind of you.
I'll get you drunk
and make you expose your filthy self!
-None for you, Yor.
-I know!
What a bummer.
So, where did you two meet?
At a boutique on Third Avenue.
I felt a stranger staring at me
-I thought, "Wow!"
-Well, you know.
It was because she's so beautiful!
That made me sound suspicious!
This topic is going to get us exposed.
I have to change the subject.
After a few more meals together,
we hit it off.
When, where, how many times,
and at which restaurants did you eat at?
How many times did you meet before dating?
What made you decide to marry her?
Um…
What's with this interrogation?
What do you two call each other?
Huh? Well… Yor and…
Yor?! Even I don't call her Yor!
Sis, what do you call him?
-Loy Loy, or Lotty or something?
-Huh?
Ahh! Lotty!
Damn it!
I just call him Loid!
The man loses his cool
when it concerns his sister…
Are you okay? Here, some water.
What does Sis like about him?
Just because he's a doctor
that can cook a little,
is handsome, tall, and considerate…
Damn it!
Relax, Yuri!
I guess the Briar family
can't handle their liquor.
By the way, Yuri,
you're a diplomat, right?
Let's change the subject.
That's such a great job.
Yor is always bragging about it.
Huh?
Dominic told me
that you went to Hugaria recently!
Huh? Oh.
It was just for work.
But you're right. It was a beautiful city.
I wish I could've shown you, Sis!
There were lots of cafes. In a restaurant
where the Empress used to go…
Was it in the capital Obda?
There are lots of delicious restaurants.
I went once a while back
for medical training.
Really?
I used to go to Carpathia a lot.
The soup made by the owner was excellent.
I ate that too!
So this wine was from Hugaria!
What a great product.
-This.
-Oh, that's…
I bought it on Hedger Street.
…something I came across
at a store on Hedger Street.
It must've been expensive.
-Probably 200 dalcs.
-No, only about 200 dalcs.
I knew it.
That's plenty expensive. Thank you.
These questions and answers.
They're one of the fictional story manuals
used by Ostania's intelligence agencies.
A template for faking a trip
to another country.
Which means, this story is a complete lie.
In fact, Carpathia's owner has
put his son in charge of the restaurant.
The price of this wine also rose to
300 dalcs due to the poor harvest.
You might be able to trick a newbie,
but it won't work on me, Yuri Briar.
I was wary when I heard he worked
for the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
Being a diplomat is like
a gateway to becoming a spy.
I had Franky check, and there is
evidence that he worked as a staff member
until about a year ago.
He must've been scouted by
the intelligence community after that.
From the bit of information I have,
this man belongs to
the domestic counterintelligence agency.
WISE's enemy, the Secret Police!
But, well,
although it's risky, it's not a bad idea
to continue our friendship
as long as he doesn't suspect
my true identity.
If I can outsmart him, he can be a
great source of information on the enemy!
I'll send you something in return.
Yuri, isn't it great that you have
such a nice older brother now?
It seems like he's hiding that identity
from Yor as well.
It may be quite easy to
keep him under control.
Yuri?
I told you I won't acknowledge him, Sis!
Who'd call someone like him a brother?!
You're being rude, Yuri!
It's just like you said.
I became a respectable member of society
and can now afford expensive liquor.
But that's all thanks to Sis!
We were poor when our parents died,
so we couldn't afford
proper learning supplies. But…
Sis is late…
I wonder if she's still working…
I'm home, Yuri!
Sis!
What happened? You're covered in blood!
What kind of a job were you doing?
Oh, don't worry! It's just blood splatters
from someone else!
Never mind that, Yuri. Look what I got!
Ta-da! The illustrated reference books
you wanted!
I got paid a lot from my part-time job,
so I bought it!
Sis…
Ta-da!
Sis worked herself to a pulp just for me.
So I decided that
I'd quickly become successful, so that
I could become a man who can protect Sis.
I was the one that was going to protect
my only blood relative.
Do you understand how I feel
when a flimsy man like you
takes the most important
person in my life?
Yuri…
Of course, I wanted you to get married
and be happy sooner or later.
But that person has to be someone
who can protect you more than me!
Are you really going to be able to
fill that role?!
-Lotty!
-Lo…
I don't want my brother to worry…
I…
love Yor as much as you do.
My daughter loves Yor too.
No. He's just acting
to convince my brother.
She's already family to me.
Even if spears were to fall,
or meteorites were to fall,
I will protect her
for the rest of my life.
The man was a blatant liar.
Did he say meteorite?!
I'm confident that I can protect her
from spears but a meteorite?!
Maybe he's quite amazing after all. How?
It's easier said than done, you liar!
Yeah! You have the face of a liar!
Oh, no!
Yuri has always been a bit sloppy.
I have the face of a liar?
Has he seen through me?
No, that can't be.
Huh? You've been married for a year
and just because your hands touched?
Huh? Are you two really married?
What are you saying?
We're always lovey-dovey.
That's right!
It's suspicious.
If you really say you're married,
prove it!
-We have our marriage certificate.
-That's not what I mean!
Kiss each other right now.
-Huh?
If you love each other,
it's easy, isn't it?
But in front of someone?
Just once, and I'll be convinced.
If you can't, I'll go and have
the marriage revoked!
This is an awful turn of events.
What should I do? No. Keep calm.
I'm Twilight, Westalis' number one spy.
I've been with numerous women
for my missions.
If my plan will proceed
with just a kiss or two…
If that's all you need.
But Loid!
We'll just do it like we normally do, Yor.
Come on.
It's necessary for our cover… But…
Wha--?
What?!
SHOW OFF HOW IN LOVE YOU ARE
Subtitle translation by: Nana Onishi